开萝尔:不用看我也知道,新来的邻居自命不凡,
Carol: I can tell without seeing them,
傲慢自大.
the new neighbors are stuck up and pretentious.
麦琪:开萝尔,你不能"以车取人",很多人都有宝马这样的豪华车.
Maggie: Carol, you can't judge them by their car, lots of people have BMW's.
开萝尔:他们在保险杠上写着"我其他的车你也买不起".
Carol: With a bumper sticker that says 'you couldn't afford my other car
either'.
麦琪:亲爱的,等你老了,
Maggie: Honey as you get older you'll realize you can't make snap judgments
你就会认识到不能对人草率地下结论.
about people.
杰森:我刚才碰到隔壁的傻瓜了.
Jason: Well I just met the jerks next door.
麦琪:杰森,你刚出去了三分钟.
Maggie: Jason you've only been out there three minutes.
杰森:是的,麦琪,
Jason: Yes Maggie and in that time the CreedMoors' manage to tell me their
就那三分钟,克里德摩尔非得告诉我他的家底,他家跟多米特拉姆普是私交.
net worth that they were personal friends of Donny Trump,
知道我是精神病医生后,他们让我推掉所有的应酬,
and when I mentioned I was a psychiatrist,
约个时间给兰斯看一下.
they wanted me to drop everything and to make an appointment with Lance.
麦琪:他们的儿子吗?
Maggie: Their son?
杰森:他们的狗.
Jason: Their dog.
克莉丝:谁的狗?
Chrissy: Who's dog?
开萝尔:我们新邻居家的.他们昨晚搬来的.
Carol: Our new neighbours, they moved in last night.
克莉丝:我上床后竟然发生了这么多的好事?
Chrissy: How come all the good stuff happens after I go to bed?
麦琪:克莉丝,你睡觉后什么也没发生,
Maggie: Chrissy, we've been over this a hundred times,
我们一直这样过来的.
nothing happens after you're asleep.
克莉丝:我醒了,早饭怎么就做好了呢?
Chrissy: And how come breakfast is ready when I wake up?
迈克:早上好,尊敬的各位.
Mike: Good morning loyal subjects.
杰森:嗨.
Jason: Hey.
迈克:哦,妈妈,你知道吗,我昨晚我醒了特别想吃你做的可口的软糖.
Mike: Oh mom you know I woke up last night just craving your fabulous home made fudge.
麦琪:真的?
Maggie: Really?
迈克:是的.
Mike: Yeah.
麦琪:有时间我给你做.
Maggie: I should make it for you sometime.
迈克 :哦,周六之前,
Mike: Oh that would be great,
你能不能做40磅,
could you make about forty pounds of it and have it cut up and wrapped
切好,用彩色玻璃纸包好呢?
in coloured cellophane by Saturday?
麦琪:不,迈克,我做不了.到底怎么了?
Maggie: No Mike I couldn't, now what's going on?
迈克:哦,伯里顿师范学院周六要举行集资活动.我答应你要做40磅的软糖.
Mike: Well Botens Date Teacher's College is having this fund raiser on Saturday and I
promised that you'd make forty pounds of fudge
麦琪:哦,你为什么不答应我会在锯琴上拉曲子呢?
Maggie: Oh, why didn't you promise I'll play show toons on a musical saw?
迈克:哦,因为我不是娱乐委员会的.
Mike: Well, cause I'm not on the entertainment committee.
麦琪:哦,迈克,你想要软糖,配方就在抽屉里,
Maggie: Oh aw, Mike you want fudge, the recipe is in the draw,
你可以多做40倍的软糖.来吧,克莉丝,我们要上学了.
multiply by forty.Come on Chrissy, let's get ready for school.
本:哦,伙计们,
Ben: Oh man, are the new neighbours cool or what?
新邻居真够酷的.我只是帮他们搬了些垃圾,就给了我5美元.
Well them carry some trash for the curb they slipped me five bucks.
开萝尔:邻里之间做点小事你就要人家的钱,真难以置信.
Carol: I can't believe you accepted cash for doing a neighbourly gesture.
本:干嘛不?你知道他们家有多少储蓄吗?
Ben: Why not?Do you know what their bank balance is?
杰森:比起他们的家产来不算什么.
Jason: Nothing compared to their net worth.
迈克:听着,本,能帮我个忙吗?
Mike: Listen Benny I need you to do a favour for me?
今天是卢克第一次去杜威高中,我想让你盯紧点他,教教他怎么做.
It's Luke's first day at Duwee High, so I just want you to stick around
with him you know show him the ropes a little bit
本:哦,算了吧,迈克,你知道他们对新生很厉害的.如果我紧跟着他,我会被当成大傻瓜的.
Ben: Oh come on Mike, you know how tough they are on new kids, I mean if I hang out with him I'll be the grand pooh ball of geek dumb.
迈克:听着,大傻瓜.你今天必须跟着他,要不我告诉妈妈你干的那些坏事.
Mike: Yeah well listen pooh, you hang out with Luke today or I'll tell mom
where her Victoria's secret catalogues were
本:卢克,我的老兄,今天跟紧点我,我教你怎么做.
Ben: Luke my home boy, stick close to me today and I'll show you the ropes.
卢克:哦,所以如果我见了你,可以说"嗨"了?
Luke: Oh, so that means if I see you I can say hi?
开萝尔:卢克,开始进正规学校了,你紧张吗?
Carol: So Luke, are you nervous about starting regular classes?
卢克:我应该知道点规矩.迈克一直在教我呢.
Luke: I should get the hang of it; Mike here has been tutoring me.
开萝尔:紧张,非常紧张.
Carol: Be nervous, be very nervous.
卓蒂:你好,你好.
Jodi: Rap tap tap.
开萝尔:哦,需要帮忙吗?
Carol: Oh, can I help you?
卓蒂:哦,你说英语,你老板在吗?
Jodi: Oh, you speak English, is your employer home?
麦琪:你肯定是克里德摩尔太太.我是麦琪西沃.
Maggie: Or you must be Mrs.CreedMoor, I'm Maggie Sever.
卓蒂:哦,你真漂亮.请叫我卓蒂.
Jodi: Oh kill for Paul, please call me Jodi.
卓蒂:老天啊.你在干什么,麦琪?
Jodi: My goodness, what are you doing Maggie?
麦琪:我在打扫烤箱呢,卓蒂.
Maggie: I'm cleaning the oven Jodi.
卓蒂:哦,这种东西也能脏?
Jodi: Oh, those things get dirty?
麦琪:是的.一般来说,
Maggie: Yes they do,
我们应该扔了,但我想可以试一试.
usually we just throw them out but I thought I'll give this a try
卓蒂:我来是想给你这个.
Jodi: I just came by to give you this.
麦琪:啊,请柬吗?
Maggie: Ah, oh an invitation?
卓蒂:哦,我和埃利周五要举行一个化装舞会.
Jodi: Ah Elli and I are just having a little house warming suore on Friday
我们决定邀请所有的人.
and we said what the heck let's just invite everybody.
麦琪:哦,我要跟我丈夫商量一下.
Maggie: Well I'll have a check with my husband.
卓蒂:哦,你会来的,一定,一定要来,好吗,邻居?
Jodi: Oh, so you'll come, please, please, please neighbour?
麦琪:好吧,我们会去的.
Maggie: Alright we'll be there.
卓蒂:哦,麦琪,我相信那一定是最美好的时刻.哦,
Jodi: Oh Maggie, well I don't know when I've have a better time well I
我得走了.半小时后,我要去见美容咨询师.
must fly I have to go meet my colour consultant in half an hour.
我应该给你她的号码.
I should give you her number;
她可以让丑八怪变成大美人.
well she can make a silk purse out of a sowzier.
麦琪:希望如此.
Maggie: I hope so.
本:卢克,伙计,第一天感觉怎么样?
Ben: Luke, my man, how was your first day?
卢克:很好.我的第一天过去了.
Luke: Fine, my first day is gone.
本:哦,新学校的第一天总是这样的.别人知道你的名字也有个过程.
Ben: Oh, first day in new school can always be tuff.May take many body know she name.
萨莎:嘿,卢克.
Sasha: Hi Luke.
卢克:萨莎萨拉科斯基今天冲我笑了,我死而无撼了.
Luke: Sasha Saracsky smiled to me today I can die I a happy man
本:你跟萨莎萨拉科斯基开玩笑了?
Ben: You kidded with Sasha Saracsky?
哲克:嗨,卢克,我的偶像.
Jerk: Hey, Luke, my star.
卢克:哲克斯特里克.
Luke: Jerk streak.
哲克:一会儿大家要到商场去玩从电动扶梯上滑下来的游戏,
Jerk: Hu, after practice the whole gang is going down to the mall to go
你想去吗?
body surfing down the escalator rails, you want to come?
卢克:太好了,我能带本去吗?
Luke: Great, can I bring Ben?
哲克:谁?
Jerk: Who?
本:我,我,
Ben: Me, Ben Sever, Benno, Benny boy.
本西沃,可爱的本.你4年级的时候差点用球杀了我.
You tried to kill me in the fourth grade with a thunder ball.
哲克:好,只要是卢克的朋友就行.
Jerk: Yeah well any friend of Luke's, wait a minute, Sever,
等等,西沃,你是那个象棋俱乐部的傻瓜队长.
you're the geek that's president of the chess club.
本:我是被选上的.
Ben: I was drafted.
哲克:你是个厉害的角色.
Jerk: You're a very powerful man.
本:实际上,我外强中干.
Ben: Actually I burst quite easily.
哲克:你是校园皇后提名委员会的吗?
Jerk: You're on the nominating committee for the home coming queen?
本:不,不是.我是诚惶诚恐说这话的.
Ben: No I'm not and I say that with the deepest respect and fear.
哲克:是的,你们俱乐部的头都在委员会.
Jerk: Yeah you are all club presidents are on the committee.
本:呃,好吧.
Ben: Eh, ok.
卢克:该走了,本.
Luke: Way to go Ben.
哲克:我想你该投堂娜肯特一票.
Jerk: I think that you should vote for Donna Kent.
本:堂娜,是"疯狂的"肯特?
Ben: Donna 'wild thing' Kent?
哲克:她是我的女朋友.
Jerk: She's my girl friend.
本:还是你的心肝.
Ben: And sweetheart too.
哲克:别弄错了.要是看到有比她漂亮的,
Jerk: Don't get me wrong you see somebody who is better vote for her you
你会选吗?一定要把她的号码告诉我.
just make sure you give me your number.
卢克:本,你要看到学校里最热辣的美女了.
Luke: Ben, you're gonna meet all the hottest girls in school.
本:不,
Ben: No I won't,
我看不到.俱乐部的头头们坐前排.
all the presidents of the cool clubs will be upfront I'm gonna be stuck
我和蜘蛛学会的音像俱乐部的人坐在后边.
in the back with the audio visual club in the Arachnid society.
卢克:哇,也许我可以给你弄个前排位置.
Luke: Whoa, maybe I could get you a front row seat.
凯特:好了,这是做软糖需要的购物单:胡萝卜粉,麦芽糖和藕粉.
Kate: Ok, here is the shopping list for the fudge; carrot powder, barley malt, arrowroot
迈克:哇,哇,哇,凯特,我们是做软糖呢,还是铺马路呢?
Mike: Wow wow wow Kate, are we making fudge or are we paving the drive way?
凯特:迈克,要是用做软糖的一般材料会坏事的.
Kate: Mike the ingredients in regular fudge will ruin your system.
迈克:凯特,哦,得了吧,
Mike: Kate, oh come on if we use your ingredients we might as well buy
如果用你的材料,我们还不如买点莴苣,然后涂成赫色就算软糖得了.
lettuce paint it brown and call it fudge.
麦琪:也许是我的电话,我在等运钻头来,
Maggie: It's probably for me I am expecting a shipment of drills to test
准备写我的专栏.
for my column.
本:西沃家.堂娜肯特?啊,是的,
Ben: Sever's residue, Donna Kent ,
嗨,堂娜.我真荣幸接到你的电话.是的,卢克在.
ah yeah hello Donna may I say what a pleasure, yeah Luke's here.
卢克:疯女,什么事?
Luke: Wild thing what's shaking?
麦琪:好了,克莉丝,8点了,该睡觉了.
Maggie: Ok Chrissy, eight o'clock bed time.
克莉丝:我想看看小狼能不能抓到小羊.
Chrissy: I want to see if the Chayote catches the road runner.
麦琪:宝贝,小狼永远都抓不到小羊的.
Maggie: Honey, the chayote never catches the road runner.
克莉丝:谢谢,你让我安心了.
Chrissy: Thanks you ruined it for me.
杰森:好了,宝贝,你妈妈都说了.
Jason: Come on sweetheart you heard your mother.
克莉丝:但我想吃东西.
Chrissy: But I need a snack.
麦琪:你吃过了.
Maggie: You had a snack.
克莉丝:我能喝点吗?
Chrissy: Can I have a drink?
麦琪:你喝过了.
Maggie: You had a drink.
克莉丝:没用米老鼠杯子喝.
Chrissy: Not in my Mickey Mouse cup.
杰森:克莉丝.
Jason: Chrissy.
克莉丝:太不公平了.为什么我非得去睡觉,而你们每个人却待着,
Chrissy: It's not fair how come I have to go to bed and everyone else
还玩.我听见你们欢歌笑语的,我知道你们做什么.
gets to stay up and have fun, I hear you laughing, I know what you do,
等到克莉丝睡觉了,你们就开舞会,舞会,舞会.
wait till Chrissy goes to bed and then party, party party.
麦琪:我们一会就陪你睡的.
Maggie: We'll be right up to tuck you in.
杰森:听着,我们新的邻居格里德摩尔家…
Jason: Well listen to this one, our new neighbours the Greedmoors.
麦琪:是克里德摩尔.
Maggie: That's Creedmoor.
杰森:是,管他呢.他们想邀请我们去他家参加舞会.真是好运.
Jason: Yeah whatever, they want us to come to their house warming party, good luck
麦琪:杰森.
Maggie: Jason.
杰森:麦琪,那可是化装舞会,
Jason: Maggie it's a costume party for crying out loud,
要大声叫喊.
you couldn't pay me to set foot on their over priced property much less
你不会给我买服装来满足他们的要求的.更遭的是还要穿一些愚蠢的…
wear some stupid...
是你答应的,是不是?
you said yes didn't you?
麦琪:我不能拒绝,他们是邻居.
Maggie: I couldn't say no they are neighbours.
杰森:哦,麦琪.
Jason: Oh Maggie.
麦琪:哦,好了,杰森.舞会很有趣.
Maggie: Oh come on Jason it'll be fun I called the costume shops and here
我给服装店打了电话,这些服装适合你的身材.你可以扮成豪猪,
are the costumes that are available in your size, you can be a porcupine,
弗雷迪科如格,快乐的鲁普鲁.
Freddie Krueger, heappy loupyu.
杰森:麦琪,我是有声望的医生.
Jason: Maggie I am a respected professional I refuse to wear anything
我拒绝穿上带羽毛,指甲或刺这种东西的服装.
with furs, finger nails or quills.
麦琪:哦,那就不去算了.
Maggie: Ah that rules out Libber Rochie.
卢克:可你会去的,是吗?
Luke: But you'll ah probably go right?
杰森:我要是能决定就好了.
Jason: Not if I have anything to say about it.
卢克:得了吧,你会去的,是吗?
Luke: Come on, then you'll probably go right?
麦琪:对.
Maggie: Right.
卢克:太好了.化装舞会总是富有节日的气愤.
Luke: Great, well I mean that costume parties are always so festive.
杰森:节日气愤,你穿着带刺的衣服能坐吗?
Jason: Festive, you've ever tried sitting down in quills?
麦琪:等我们哄克莉丝睡了再谈论吧.
Maggie: Let's talk about it after we tuck Chrissy in.
卢克:本,你周五有什么计划?
Luke: Ben, what are your plans for this Friday?
本:什么都不做.我想独自在家,
Ben: I'm doing nothing,
坐在我屋里直呆呆地看天花板,
I'll be home alone sitting in my room looking at the same spot on the sealing,
听着时钟滴答作响,把我悲惨的生命带走.
listening to the clock ticking away the minutes of my pathetic existence.
卢克:好.别做其他的事,好吗?
Luke: Good, don't make any other plans alright?
麦琪:宝贝,你想喝水吗?
Maggie: Honey, would you like a sip of water?
克莉丝:不.
Chrissy: No.
杰森:想听故事吗?
Jason: How about a quick story.
克莉丝:不.
Chrissy: No.
麦琪:来个吻别?
Maggie: How about a good night kiss?
克莉丝:随便你.
Chrissy: If you must.
麦琪:做个美梦,宝贝.
Maggie: Sweet dreams honey.
杰森:晚安,小宝贝.
Jason: Good night sweet heart.
克莉丝:哦,看来又剩下我和你了,博格尔先生.他们人都在楼下玩,却不要我.等一下,这次我要亲自去看看.
Chrissy: Well it seems like its me and you again Mr.Bogel, everybody's downstairs having
fun without me, wait a minute, this time I'm going see for myself
杰森:我想,克莉丝这会儿一定睡着了.
Jason: Well I guess Chrissy must be asleep by now.
麦琪:今晚你要干什么?
Maggie: What do you want to do tonight?
杰森:我不知道,你想玩芭比娃娃吗?
Jason: Woo I don't know, you want to play barbies?
麦琪:好的,小伙子们,我们想玩芭比娃娃,你们来玩吗?
Maggie: Ok guys we are gonna play barbies, you all want to join us?
卢克:克莉丝睡了,晚会开始了.
Luke: Chrissy is asleep and the party is starting.
麦琪:孩子们,如果你们想在沙发上跳的话,那就重重地跳,里面的弹簧需要锻炼.
Maggie: Boys if you are going to jump hard on the sofa you need to
jump harder the spring needs the exercise
本:你从哪里弄来的?太漂亮了.
Ben: Where did you get these they're gorgeous.
杰森:圣诞老人送的,我一直在等待特别的场合拿出来.
Jason: Santa Claus brought them, I was just waiting for a special occasion.
本:我知道,我们看电视吧,都坐到屏幕近前来.
Ben: I know let's watch TV and stay real close to the screen.
卢克:不,我们每天晚上都这样.
Luke: No we do that every night.
麦琪:我想玩点新鲜的,来个茶会怎么样?
Maggie: I want to play something else, I know tea party.
凯特:我想玩化装游戏.
Kate: I want to play dress up.
卢克:哦,跳绳,跳绳.
Luke: Ah jump rope, jump rope.
杰森:我们时间有的是,可以玩个通宵.
Jason: We have time for everything, we have all night.
迈克:我们玩什么还不都一样吗?没有克莉丝,
Mike: What difference does it make what we do?
什么都好办.
As long as we do it without Chrissy.
麦琪:我知道,我知道.
Maggie: I know, I know, let's have something from the basic four groups;
我们从这四样食物里选一样吃的:比萨饼,爆米花,冰激凌和糖果.
pizza, popcorn, ice cream and candy.
本:我打不开.谁递给我一把剪刀?
Ben: I can't this chips open can somebody pass me some scissors?
卢克:你要剪刀干嘛?你有脚,不是吗?
Luke: Why do you need scissors for, you got feet don't you?
本:是啊.
Ben: Yeah.
麦琪:谁吃东西?好了,我拿来蔬菜了.
Maggie: Who wants cavities?Ok I brought you some vegetables.
迈克:哦,妈妈,你疯了吗?
Mike: Oh mom are you crazy?
凯特:不是吃的,是拿来扔的.
Katie: Not for eating for throwing.
杰森:嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,这些沙发垫是用来踩的,不是用来打的.
Jason: Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey, those sofa cushions are not for hitting.they're making for feet.
卢克:葡萄汁,我最喜欢的.
Luke: Grape, my favorite.
本:出不来了.
Ben: There were never come out.
卢克:这都怪克莉丝,噢.
Luke: Let's blame it on Chrissy.Yeah.
开萝尔:嘿,你们又不带克莉丝玩上了?
Carol: Hey are you guys playing without Chrissy again?
每个人:对.
Everyone: Yeah
开萝尔:太好了,看我给你们拿什么来了.
Carol: Well that's great because look what I brought pony rides for everyone.
克莉丝:我懂了.我抓着你们了.
Chrissy: I knew it I caught you.
杰森:啊,我们该怎么做啊?
Jason: Ah, what should we do?
迈克:让她回去睡觉.
Mike: Put her back to bed.
每个人:让她回去睡觉.
Everyone chanting: Put her back to bed.
克莉丝:住嘴,住嘴,住嘴,住嘴.
Chrissy: Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it.
麦琪:克莉丝,怎么了?
Maggie: Chrissy, what is it?
克莉丝:我再也不回去睡觉了.
Chrissy: That's it I'm never going to sleep again.
麦琪:她现在睡了.
Maggie: Now she sleeps.
杰森:我想她肯定彻夜难眠的,麦琪.
Jason: I don't think she closed her eyes once one night Maggie,
也许我们该想个别的办法了.
maybe it's time we tried something different.]
麦琪:什么办法?让她做俯卧撑,直到晕过去?
Maggie: Like what?Make her do military push ups until she passes out?
杰森:想个,啊,
Jason: Or like ah why don't we let her stay up as late as she wants
为什么不让她跟我们在一起,不管多晚,让她看看我们并没做什么.
one night and let her see that nothing happens.
麦琪:你这主意听起来很有趣,就像另一个国家的另一个家庭的另一个孩子,
Maggie: That sounds like a interesting idea with another child and another
甚至是在另一个时空里的一样.
family and another country perhaps in a separate but parallel universe.
杰森:她睡觉的时间是8点,她需要睡觉.
Jason: Her bed time is eight o'clock she needs to sleep.
杰森:这就像再添一张桌子一样容易.
Jason: Is this how you want her to get it tasting table?
麦琪:如果她赖着不走怎么办?
Maggie: Well what if she likes staying up?
如果她整天都这样怎么办?
What if she wants to do it all the time?
杰森:不会的,麦琪;我们一定要让那一天成为她一生中最乏味的一天.
Jason: She won't Maggie; we would make sure that is the most boring, un event full night of your life?
麦琪:那我们怎么办的到呢?
Maggie: And how would we do that?
杰森:行了,我没必要告诉你怎么让晚上枯燥.你那么兴奋,
Jason: Come on I don't have to tell you how to make a night boring,
那么有活力,只是因为你是个成年人.但对一个孩子,
I mean you are very you are exciting and dynamic and tingly but you're
她不会理解的.这是因为,
an adult but to a kid she wouldn't understand,
好了,我还要说什么呢?我们试试吧.
and its because come on what do you have to say?Let's give it a shake.
麦琪:好吧,杰森,你把我说通了.
Maggie: Ok Jason you sweet talk me into it but if it back fires nothing
不过如果事与愿违,你也给我按时睡觉,不能做任何事.
happens after your bed time either.
杰森:来吧,克莉丝,宝贝,过来.该上学了,快点.
Jason: Come on Chrissy sweet heart come on time for school come on.
克莉丝:小马来了吗?
Chrissy: Is a pony here?
杰森:不,没有.我想跟你做个交易.第二天上学的每个晚上你必须按时睡觉;不上学的晚上可以跟我们在一起,多晚都没关系.
Jason: No there's not, I am gonna make you a deal I want you to go to bed on every school night and then the first non-school night you can stay up as long as you want.
克莉丝:真的?
Chrissy: Really?
杰森:真的.
Jason: Really yes.We want you to see what we all do after you go to
我们想让你知道你睡觉后我们都干什么.
bed.
克莉丝:我们能拉钩吗?
Chrissy: Do you pinky swear?
杰森:我们拉钩.
Jason: I pinky swear.
麦琪:好了,克莉丝穿上毛衣,我们去上学.
Maggie: Ok Chrissy go get your sweater and I'll take you to school.
克莉丝:好的.
Chrissy: Ok.
杰森:我认为这是良好的开始.
Jason: I call that an auspicious beginning.
麦琪:我认为这是屈服.你别忘了,"佛洛伊德医生",下次不上学的晚上是周五,但那天有克里德摩尔家的化装晚会.
Maggie: And I call it caving in and another thing Doctor Floyd and that the
next non-school night is Friday and that's the CreedMoors' costume party
杰森:太好了.有点失望,麦琪,我们只能取消了.
Jason: That's great a little disappointing to me Maggie we'll have to cancel.
麦琪:杰森.
Maggie: Jason.
杰森:麦琪,我能怎么办啊?我都拉钩了.
Jason: Maggie, come on what can I do?I pinky swore.
凯特:这就是软糖业的噩梦啊.
Katie: This looks like night mare on Fudge Street.
迈克:嘿,放松,我们做完了.
Mike: Hey relax, we are done.
凯特:真不敢相信我帮你做了40磅的软糖.
Katie: I can't believe I help you make forty pounds of this stuff do you
你知道这里有多少脂肪吗?
know how much fat is in this?
我们为什么不去市场摆个摊,把这些"猪油"都卖了?
Why didn't I just go to the Big Sale set up a booth and sell lard?
迈克:凯特,记住,这是为了伟大的事业.
Mike: Kate come on remember this is for a very very good cause.
凯特:什么事业?
Katie: Which is?
迈克:在学生会里放了一个新的制糖机.
Mike: Putting a new candy machine in the student union.
凯特:为了这就让我剥了25磅胡桃壳?
Katie: For that I shelled twenty five pounds of walnuts?
迈克:嘿,嘿,
Mike: Hey hey hey,
嘿,
I was the one who wanted to leave them in the shell you were the one
我并不想把胡桃的壳剥了,是你担心会把人们的牙给硌了.
worried about cracking people's teeth.
现在听着,我去开车来把糖都装上,好吗?
Right now listen up I'll go the wagon so we can load it up ok?
凯特:我们要运到哪去啊?
Katie: Where do we have to deliver all of this?
迈克:嘿,我这有地址.
Mike: Hey I got the address right here.
凯特:迈克,你不觉得你忽略了这上面的一些重要信息吗?
Katie: Mike do you think there might be some important information you've overlooked here
迈克:哦,该放到可循环利用的纸上吗?
Mike: Ah, bring it on recycled paper?
凯特:大拍卖是在下个月.
Katie: The big sale is next month.
迈克:你知道一个偷懒的女人就是疯子,亲爱的,
Mike: You know a lesser woman would be mad honey,
你别激动.
I got to hit it to you.
凯特:我花了整个下午熬汤,
Kate: I spent the entire afternoon cooking liquid deft because you can't
就是因为你不会看说明书吗?
read instructions?
迈克:亲爱的,很抱歉.我对日期一直不敏感.你原谅我吗?
Mike: Honey look I am sorry I've never been good with dates, you forgive me?
凯特:让软糖见鬼去吧.
Kate: Eat fudge and die.
麦琪:我找管理员.好的,我不挂.克莉丝,8点了,把电视闭了.
Maggie: I want to talk to his supervisor, yes I'll hold, Chrissy it's eight o'clock the TV goes off.
克莉丝:好极了,舞会时间到了.
Chrissy: Great time to party.
杰森:今天我们让你这么晚不睡觉是为了让你知道没有舞会.现在,过来,坐好,让我们静静地享受吧.
Jason: Look the reason we made you stay up so late tonight is to see that there is no party.Now come on just sit back and let's enjoy the quiet.
麦琪:听着,先生.都一个星期了,你每次都对我说对不起.现在都星期五晚上了.
Maggie: Listen to me Mr.on time every time you've been giving me that sorry song for over a week now and it is Friday night,
你今晚必须把钻头送来.否则,
you get me those drills tonight or else I am coming down there with a
我会带上一把大剪刀去把你的信箱破开.
pair of hedge clippers and I'm gonna open your mail,
对,我很厉害.
that's right I play rough.
克莉丝:真无聊.我们能订个比萨吗?
Chrissy: This is boring, Can we order pizza?
杰森:不,克莉丝.在平常的晚上,我们不吃什么特殊食品的.
Jason: No Chrissy, on normal nights we don't have any special treats.
迈克:好了.给大家吃糖.
Mike: Ok, fudge for everyone.
克莉丝:哇.
Chrissy: Wow.
麦琪:克莉丝,平时不这样的.
Maggie: Chrissy, this is unusual.
克莉丝:对,我可以吃点吗?
Chrissy: Right, can I have some?
杰森:如果你喝牛奶的话,就可以.
Jason: Only if you have some milk to go along with it
克莉丝:没问题.
Chrissy: No problem.
卢克:你父母在这干嘛呢?
Luke: What are you parents doing here?
本:哦,我们得忍着点.这可是他们的地盘.
Ben: Well we have to put up with them they own the place.
卢克:我本来以为他们要出去的.
Luke: I thought they were going out tonight.
本:看起来不像啊.他们出去干嘛?我们也出去吧.
Ben: It doesn't look like it, so what's the big deal?We'll go out then.
卢克:你不能.
Luke: You can't.
本:为什么啊?
Ben: Why not?
卢克:因为你是捣蛋鬼,这是为你好.
Luke: Because you're a mess, it's for you.
本:如果外边有只燃烧的口袋,你死定了.
Ben: If there's a flaming bag out there you're dead meat.
女士:嗨,本西沃住这里吗?
Lady: Hi does Ben Sever live here?
本:是,我就是本.
Ben: Yeah, I'm Ben.
堂娜:我是堂娜肯特.你也许听过我的外号-"疯女".坐好了,我要跳舞了.
Donna: I'm Donna Kent, you may know me as 'Wild Thing'.You sit I'll dance.
本:好.
Ben: Ok.
凯特:这里干什么呢?
Katie: What's going on here?
堂娜:这里在举行学校皇后大赛呢.
Donna: This is the talent competition for home coming queen.
本:是吗?我还以为下周在学校举行呢.
Ben: It is?I thought that was next week at school?
迈克:别跟"疯女"拌嘴.
Mike: Well don't argue with the 'wild thing'.
堂娜:就在这里,今晚.
Donna: It's definitely here tonight.
本:我还真想不出个所以然来.卢克,卢克,一定是他干的.
Ben: It says alright I just can't figure out, Luke, Luke must have done this.
凯特:我不相信他们能克服困难把姑娘们带来.
Kate: I can't believe they'll go through all this trouble to get girls.
迈克:那个孩子是个天才.
Mike: The kid's got talent.
克莉丝:她一定以为我早睡了.
Chrissy: I guess she must have figured out I was in bed.
麦琪:克莉丝,我不知道出什么事了,可我肯定…
Maggie: Chrissy I don't know what's going on here but I'm sure there's...,
杰森:我去开门,哈哈.
Jason: I'll get it, Ah ha
克莉丝:快看啊.
Chrissy: Look that!
麦琪:你找谁啊?
Maggie: May I help you?
卓蒂:说什么呢?我是你的新邻居-卓蒂克里德摩尔.
Jodi: Say what?Your new neighbour Jody Creedmoor.
麦琪:哦,对不起,我没认出来.还记得我丈夫杰森吗?
Maggie: Oh I'm sorry I didn't recognize you, You remember my husband Jason?
杰森:是,很高兴再见到你.我很喜欢你头上戴的这个.
Jason: Yeah nice to see you again, I like that Marge Simpson thing you got going?
卓蒂:我感到很遗憾,你不能去寒舍参加舞会.所以我带了这个盘子来.
Jody: I felt just awful that you weren't gonna come to my little doo so I brought popo platter
克莉丝:比萨圈?
Chrissy: Pizza roll?
卓蒂:是晒干的西红柿和抹了羊奶的玉米饼
Jody: Sun dried tomatoes and goat cheese in a tortilla skin.
克莉丝:对,是比萨圈.
Chrissy: Right, pizza roll.
杰森:这只是巧合罢了.
Jason: This is just a coincidence.
麦琪:哦,你太好了,卓蒂.
Maggie: Oh this is so sweet of you Jodi.
卓蒂:哦,我只能做这点小事.呃,我家的抽水马桶堵了,
Jody: Oh, it's the least I could do, by the by our plumbing has gone kerfluee,
能不能让我最好的几个朋友用一下你们家的洗手间啊?
would it be alright if a few of my very closest friends could used your
bathroom?
麦琪:哦,当然.
Maggie: Oh sure.
卓蒂:谢谢.
Jody: Fluuuy.
麦琪:在楼上.
Maggie: It's upstairs.
克莉丝:哦.
Chrissy: Ohhhh.
卢克:对不起,啊.
Luke: Excuse me, Aw.
杰森:上楼,在右边,跟着豪猪.
Jason: Upstairs on the right follow the porcupine .
男人:我是来给麦琪马龙送货的.
Man: I got a delivery here for Maggie Malon
麦琪:哦,太好了.我的钻头终于来了.
Maggie: Oh great, my drills are finally here.
男人:钻头?夫人,签收的是一车洋娃娃啊,把她们搬进来.
Man: Drills, Lady you just signed for a truck load of dolls, bring them on in.
麦琪:哦,等等,小伙子们,这一定是…
Maggie: Oh wait guys they must be some.
男人:放这儿,还是放草坪上?你选吧.
Man: In here or on the lawn it's your choice.
克莉丝:我来了,我来了.谢谢你.吃点糖.
Chrissy: I'm here I'm here, thank you, have some fudge.
克莉丝:啵,啵,啵.
Chrissy: Bo bo bo.
麦琪:克莉丝,这是个很大的错误.
Maggie: Chrissy this is all a big mistake.
杰森:以前从未发生的这样的事.
Jason: Nothing like this has ever happened before.
克莉丝:啊,哈,啊,太好了.
Chrissy: Ah ha, ah cool.
凯特:迈克,你干什么呢?
Kate: Mike, what are you doing?
迈克:她很有灵性.你喜欢吗?
Mike: Gotta ....spirit, what did you like that ah thing?
女孩:本西沃在这里吗?
Girl: Is Ben Sever here.
本:噢.
Ben: Yow.
女孩:我叫普利斯托.
Girl: Pristo.
卢克:西沃先生现在很忙,坐那里,等着叫你的名字.
Luke: Mr.Sever is busy right now, have a seat and wait until your name is called.
女孩:不行.她们早就开始了.
Girl: No way they started without us.
麦琪:没办法了.
Maggie: I give up.
杰森:开萝尔.
Jason: Carol,
开萝尔:我刚考完期中考试,熬了两夜,我只想到自己的床上睡一觉.
Carol: I finish mid terms pull two all night up all I want to do is sleep in my own bed.
麦琪:开萝尔,在这里你可找不到安静的地方.
Maggie: Carol, you're not gonna get any quiet around here.
开萝尔:没关系的.我困死了.
Carol: That's ok I'm totally wrecked.
男人:哦,我可以用一下洗手间吗?
Man: Oh could we use the bathroom?
开萝尔:当然,跟我来.
Carol: Sure follow me.
克莉丝:哦,妈妈,爸爸,每件事都是我梦想的.我再也不早睡觉了.
麦琪:多巧的事啊.你可不是这样的.
Chrissy: Pony, Mummy daddy everything I've ever dreamed, I'm never going to bed again. Maggie
What a coincidence, neither are you